A Guide to the Foundation for Child Development records FA019
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Financial Records, 1964-1992, 1996; 3
  - Reprints, 1954-1974; 5
    - Reprints (G) (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Gruenwald, P. "Lobular Architecture and Maternal Blood Supply of Primate Placentas." "Medical Primatology," Part I, Proceedings 3rd Conference exp. Medical Surgical Primate, Long, (Karger, Basel 1972): 248-254.
    - Reprints (H) (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Hsu, Lillian Y. F. and Kurt Hirschhorn. "Unusual Turner Mosaicism (45,X/47,XXX;45,XXqi;45,X/46,XXR): Detection Through Deceleration from Normal Linear Growth or Secondary Amenorrhea." "Journal of Pediatrics" 79, no. 2 (August 1971): 276-281.
      Huckabee, William E., Crenshaw Carlyle, Curet, Luis B. and Donald H. Barron. "Uterine Blood Flow and Oxygen Consumption in the Unrestrained Pregnant Ewe." "Quarterly Journal of Experimental Physiology" 57, (1972): 12-23.
    - Reprints (I) (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Dawson, Blanche, Horobin, Gordon, Illsley, Raymond* and Ross Mitchell. "A Survey of Childhood Asthma in Aberdeen." "The Lancet" (April 19, 1969): 827-830.
      Illsley, R. and D. G. Gill. "Changing Trends in Illegitimacy." "Social Science and Medicine" 2, (1968): 415-433.
    - Reprints (K) (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Horowitz, Frances Degen. "Visual Attention, Auditory Stimulation and Language Discrimination in Young Infants." With Commentary by Robert B. McCall and Jerome Kagan*. "Society for Research in Child Development," Serial No. 158, 39, nos. 5-6, (December 1974).
      Kahn, Richard D. "Regulation of Privately Supported Foundations: Some Anomalies." "Indiana Legal Forum" 4, no. 1 (Fall 1970): 271-304.
      Kalimo, Esko. "Determinants of Medical Care Utilization." "Research Institute for Social Security" Series #: 11, A Division of the National Pensions Institute (Helsinki: National Pensions Institute, 1959), 1-47.
      Kamerman, Sheila. "Developing a Family Impact Statement." "An Occasional Paper from the Foundation for Child Development" (May 1976).
      Kessner, David M. and Carolyn Kalk. "A Strategy for Evaluation Health Services: Conclusions, Recommendations and Summary." "Contrasts in Health Status" 2 (Washington, D. C.: Institute of Medicine, National Academy of Sciences, 1973).
      Kessner, David M., Kalk, Carolyn Snow and James Singer. "Assessment of Medical Care for Children: Conclusions and Summary." "Contrasts in Health Status" 3 (Washington, D. C.: Institute of Medicine, National Academy of Sciences, 1974).
      Kessner, David M., Singer, James, Kalk, Carolyn E. and Edward R. Schlesinger. "Infant Death: An Analysis by material Rish and Health Care: Conclusions, Recommendation and Summary." "Contrasts in Health Status" 1 (Washington, D. C.: Institute of Medicine, National Academy of Sciences, 1973).
      Klapper, Zelda S. "Reading Retardation: II. Psychoeducational Aspects of Reading Disabilities." "Pediatrics" 37, no. 2 (February 1966): 366-376.
    - Reprints (L) (Box 4, Folder 12)
      Birch, Herbert G. and Arthur Lefford*. "Intersensory Development in Children." With Commentary by Robert B. McCall and Jerome Kagan*. "Society for Research in Child Development, Inc." Serial No. 89, 28, no. 5, (1963).
      Lessing, Lawrence. "DNA: at the core of life itself, The Biology Revolution I, II, III." "Fortune" (March 1966): 146-152.
      Luscher, Kurt. "The Child in Contemporary Society." Notes on the first Wolfsberg Conference, June 17 - July 3, 1976. "Wolfsberg Bulletin Number One" (May 1977).
    - Reprints (M) (Box 5, Folder 13)
      McFarland, Ross A. "Youth and the Automobile." "Association for the Aid of Crippled Children," Golden Anniversary White House Conference on Children and Youth, Inc. (New York: 1960).
      Matthiessen, Martin Ebbe. "Histokemiske og Morfologiske Undersogelser af Tandudviklingen hos Humane Fostre. FADLs Forlag" (Copenhagen: 1973).
      Mayo, Leonard. The Philosophy of the Association for the Aid of Crippled Children in Relation to Grants for Medical Research. Pediatrics 19, Part II, No. 4 (April 1957): 788-792.
      Mechanic, David. "General Medical Practice in England and Wales: Its Organization and Future." "The New England Journal of Medicine" 279 (September 26, 1968): 680-689.
      Meyer, W. W. and J. Lind. "Calcifications of Iliac Arteries in Newborns and Infants." "Archives of Disease in Childhood" 47, no. 253 (June 1972): 364-372.
      Meyerson, Bjorn A. "Ontogeny of Interhemispheric Functions: An Electrophysiological Study in Pre- and Postnatal Sleep." "ACTA Physiologica Scandinavica," Supplement 312 (Stockholm: Department of Physiology, Karolinska Institute, 1968).
      Moyer, Lisel. "Planning a Health Program for Your Day Care Center." Manual on Organization, Financing and Administration of Day Care Centers (New York: Day Care Consultation Service, Bank Street College of Education, 1971).
      Murphy, H. B. M. Foster Home Variables and Adult Outcomes. "Mental Hygiene" 48, no. 4 (October 1964).
      Related Archival Materials note
      See also Box 6, Folder 22.
    - Reprints (N) (Box 5, Folder 14)
      Normand, I. C. S., R. E. Olver, E. O. R. Reynolds and L. B. Strang. "Breakdown in Alveolar Barrier to Macromolecules as a Factor in the Pathogenesis of Hyaline Membrane Disease." "International Congress of Pediatrics" (Austria: August 29 - September 4, 1971).
      Normand, I. C. S., R. E. Olver, E. O. R. Reynolds and L. B. Strang. "Permeability of Lung Capillaries and Alveoli to Non-Electrolytes in the Foetal Lamb." "Journal of Physiology" 219 (1971): 303-330.
    - Reprints (P) (Box 5, Folder 15)
      Paltrowitz, Irving M., Hirshaut, Yashar, Papenhausen, Peter, Henley, Walter, Hirschhorn, Kurt and Philip R. Glade. "Establishment of Lymphoid Cell Lines in Patients with Common Viral Diseases." "The Mount Sinai Journal of Medicine" 38, no. 3 (May-June 1971).
      Fabiani, A. D., Schiffer, P. Paoletti*, E. Grossi Paoletti. "Histochemical Evaluation of Hydrolytic Enzymes in Tumors Induced in the Rat by Nitrosourea Derivatives." "Acta neuropath." 15 (Berl. 1970): 272-278.
    - Reprints (R) (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Randal, Judith. "The Bright Promise of Neighborhood Health Centers." "The Reporter" (March 21, 1968).
      Reynell, Joan K. "Post-operative Disturbances Observed in Children with Cerebral Palsy." "Development Medicine and Child Neurology" 7, no. 4 (August 1965): 360-376.
      Richards, Martin. "Cultural and Social Influences in Infancy and Early Childhood." Burg Wartenstein Symposium No. 57, Social Class and the Early Development of Children in Britain. Wenner-Gren Foundation for Anthropological Research, (New York: June 18-26, 1973).
      Richardson, Stephen A. "Age and Sex Differences in Values toward Physical Handicaps." "Journal of Health & Social Behavior" 11, no. 3 (September 1970): 207-214.
      Richardson, S. A., Birch, H. G., Grabie, E. and K. Yoder. "The Behavior of Children in School Who Were Severely Malnourished in the First Two Years of Life." "Journal of Health and Social Behavior" 13 (September 1972): 276-284.
      Richardson, Stephen A., Goodman, Norman, Hastorf, Albert H. and Sanford M. Dornbusch. "Cultural Uniformity in Reaction to Physical Disabilities." "American Sociological Review" 26, no. 2 (April 1961): 243-247.
      Richardson, Stephen A. "Ecology of Malnutrition: Non-nutritional Factors Influencing Intellectual and Behavioral Development in Nutrition, the Nervous System, and Behavior." Scientific Publication no. 251, Pan American Health Organization.
      Richardson, Stephen A. "The Effect of Physical Disability on The Socialization of a Child" in "Handbook of Socialization Theory and Practice" (New York: Rand McNally & Company, 1969): 1047-1964.
      Richardson, Stephen A., Hastorf, Albert H. and Sanford M. Dornbusch. "Effects of Physical Disability on a Child's Description of Himself." "Child Development" 35, no. 3 (September 1964): 893-907.
      Richardson, Stephen A. "Handicap, Appearance and Stigma." "Social Science & Medicine" 5, (1971): 621-628.
      Richardson, Stephen A. "Patterns of Medical and Social Research in Pediatrics." "Acta Paediatrica Scandinavica" 59 (1970): 265-272.
      Richardson, Stephen A. "People with Cerebral Palsy Talk for Themselves." "Developmental Medicine and Child Neurology" 14 (1972): 524-535.
      Richardson, Stephen A., Herbert G. Birch and Margaret E. Hertzig. "School Performance of Children Who Were Severely Malnourished in Infancy." "American Journal of Mental Deficiency" 77, no. 5 (1973): 623-632.
      Richardson, Stephen A. and Matthew J. Friedman. "Social Factors Related to Children's Accuracy in Learning Peer Group Values Towards Handicaps." "Human Relations" 26, no. 1 (1973): 77-87.
      Richardson, Stephen A. "Some Social Psychological Consequences of Handicapping." "Pediatrics" (August 1963).
      Richardson, Stephen A. "Some Unintended Consequences of Current Rehabilitation Practices." Staff Reprint, Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1960.
      Goodman, Norman, Richardson, Stephen A.*, Dornbusch, Sanford M. and Albert H. Hastorf. "Variant Reactions to Physical Disabilities." "American Sociological Review" 28, No. 3 (June 1963): 429-435.
      Richardson, S. A. and A. Green. "When is Black Beautiful? Coloured and White Children's Reactions to Skin Colour." "The British Journal of Educational Psychology" 41, Part 1 (February 1971): 62-69.
      Richardson, Stephen A. and David Klein. "Who is the Child with a Physical Handicap? Golden Anniversary White House Conference on Children and Youth, Inc." Staff Reprint, Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1960.
      Rutter, Michael, Korn, Sam and Herbert G. Birch. "Genetic and Environmental Factors in the Development of Primary Reaction Patterns." "British Journal of Social Clinical Psychology" 2 (1963): 161-173. (see section 'B', Birch)
    - Reprints (Sc-Sp) (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Schoenfeld, Robert L. "Computer Retrieval of Epidemiological Data." "Archives of Environmental Health" 19, (November 1969): 726-739.
      Schloesser, Patricia T. "The Abused Child." "Bulletin of the Menninger Clinic" 28, no. 5 (September 1964): 260-268.
      Senn, Milton J. E. "Insights on the Child Development Movement in the United States. Monographs of the Society for Research in Child Development." Series No. 161, 4, nos. 3-4 (Chicago: University of Chicago, 1975).
      Shapiro, Sam, Weinblatt, Eve, Frank, Charles W., Sager, Robert V. and Paul M. Densen. "The H.I.P. Study of Incidence and Prognosis of Coronary Heart Disease: Methodology." "Journal of Chronic Disease" 16 (1963): 1281-1992.
      Siegel, Gerald M. and Kenneth E. Donovan. "Verbal Behavior of Retarded Children in Interpersonal Assemblies With Adults." "American Journal of Mental Deficiency" 69, no. 2 (September 1964): 244-252.
      Smith, Emily A., Ricketts, Betty M. and Sarah H. Smith. "The Recommendation for Child Placement by a Psychiatric Clinic." "The American Journal of Orthopsychiatry" 32, no. 1 (January 1962): 42-52.
      Spencer, Margaret Beal. "Personal-Social Adjustment of Minority Group Children, Part II." Emory University.
    - Reprints (St-Su) (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Stedman, Donald J. and Dorothy H. Eichorn. "A Comparison of the Growth and Development of Institutionalized and Home-Reared Mongoloids During Infancy and Early Childhood." "American Journal of Mental Deficiency" 69, no. 3 (November 1964): 391-401.
      Stein, Z. A. and M. W. Susser. "Socio-Medical Study of Enuresis Among Delinquent Boys." "British Journal of Preventive and Social Medicine" 19, no. 4 (October 1965): 174-181.
      Stone, Jeannette G. "Study Guide for Three Films on Kibbutz Infancy: Rearing Kibbutz Babies Infant Development in the Kibbutz Day Care for the Kibbutz Toddler." (New York: Institute for Child Mental Health) 1974.
      Strasser, Helmut, Sievert, Gunhild and Knut Munk. "Das korperbehinderte Kind." Carl Marhold Verlagsbuchhandlung Deutschland (Berlin-Charlottenburg: 1968).
      Suchman, Edward A. and Alfred L. Scherzer. "Current Research in Childhood Accidents." Association for the Aid of Crippled Children (New York: 1960).
    - Reprints (Sw) (Box 5, Folder 19)
      Swinyard, Chester A. "The Child With Spina Bifida." Association for the Aid of Crippled Children (New York: 1964).
      Swinyard, Chester A. "The Child With Spina Bifida," 2nd ed. (New York: Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1964).
      Swinyard, Chester A. "The Child With Spina Bifida," 3rd ed. (New York: Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1969).
      Swinyard, Chester A. "The Child With Spina Bifida," 4th ed. (New York: Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1971).
      Swinyard, Chester A. "The Child With Spina Bifida," 5th ed. (New York: Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1975) Patient Publication No. 6, Institute of Rehabilitation Medicine, New York University Medical Center.
      Swinyard, Chester A. "The Child With Spina Bifida," French ed. (New York: Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1964).
      Swinyard, Chester A. "The Child With Spina Bifida," Japanese ed. (New York: Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1964).
      Swinyard, Chester A. "The Child With Spina Bifida," Portuguese ed. (New York: Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1971).
      Swinyard, Chester A. "The Child With Spina Bifida," Spanish ed. (New York: Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1965).
    - Reprints (T) (Box 5, Folder 20)
      Talbot, Nathan B. "Has Psychologic Malnutrition Taken the Place of Rickets and Scurvy in Contemporary Pediatric Practice?" "Pediatrics" (June 1963): 909-918.
    - Reprints (V) (Box 5, Folder 21)
      Valle Consultants, Ltd. "What Holds Sami Back: A Study of Service Delivery in a Puerto Rican Community" (Flushing, New York: 1974).
      Verhoestraete, Louis J. and Ruth R. Puffer. "A World View," in "The Challenge of Fetal Loss, Prematurity, and Infant Mortality." Paper presented at the annual meeting of the Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, New York, New York, 1956. (see section 'B', Baumgartner)
    - Reprints (W) (Box 6, Folder 22)
      Walsh, S. Zoe. "The Electrocardiogram in Health Full-Term and Premature Infants." (Stockholm, Sweden 1974). Department of Pediatrics, Karolinska Sjukhuset and the Wenner-Gren Research Laboratory, Norrtulls Sjukhus.
      Wallgren, Goran (ed.). "Quantitative Studies of the Human Neonatal Circulation." "Acta Paediatrica Scandinavica" Supplement 179 (Stockholm: 1967).
      Warkany, Josef (ed.). "Congenital Malformations." "Pediatrics" 19, Part II, no. 4 (April 1957): 725-733.
      See also Box 5, Folder 13.
    - Reprints (Y) (Box 6, Folder 23)
      Yankauer, Alfred, John P. Connelly and Jacob J. Feldman. "A Survey of Allied Health Worker Utilization in Pediatric Practice in the Massachusetts and in the United States." "Pediatrics" 42, no. 5 (November 1968): 733-742.
    - Pamphlets (Box 6, Folder 24)
      "Publications of the Association for the Aid of Crippled Children." (New York, Association for the Aid of Crippled Children).
      National Committee for Research in Neurological Disorders. "Exploring the Brain of Man: In Search of Prevention and Cure of Neurological and Sensory Disorders." (New York: Association for the Aid of Crippled Children).
      "Family Impact Seminar: An Introduction." (Washington, D. C., Institute for Educational Leadership, 1977). A Program of the George Washington University's Institute for Educational Leadership.
      "The Current Program." (New York, Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1962).
      "The Child With Brain Damage." Proceedings of the 1959 Annual Meeting of the Association for the Aid of Crippled Children.
    - Pamphlets (Box 6, Folder 25)
      Association for the Aid of Crippled Children. "The Place of Persons with Disabilities in Our Society." Summary Report of Round Tables held in Preparation for Annual Meeting, 1957.
      "Current Research on the Placenta and Fetal Membranes," 2nd Printing. (New York, Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, January 1960). Subcommittee on the Study of Investigations of the Committee on the Survey of the Placenta and Fetal Membranes.
      "Resuscitation of Newborn Infants: A Report by a Special Committee on Infant Mortality of the Medical Society of the County of New York." "Obstetrics and Gynecology" 8, no. 3 (September 1956).
- Grant Programs, 1911, 1946-1996, bulk 1960-1996; bulk; 4
  This series is arranged in 6 subseries:
  Subseries 1 - Administration
  Subseries 2 - Child Trends, Inc.
  Subseries 3 - Ecology of Human Development Program
  Subseries 4 - General Grants
  Subseries 5 - State of the Child Program
  Subseries 6 - Young Scholars Program
  - Grant Programs - Administration, 1911, 1946-1989, 1995-1996 1979-1989; 1
    General correspondence, grant list summaries, historical review information, and Presidential Search committee recommendations (1995-1996) are found within this subseries.
    - Series 4.1 - Grant Programs - Administration, 1911, 1946-1989, 1995-1996 (Reel 40, Frame 153)
    - Bio-Social Research Division Proposal, 1968 (Reel 40, Frame 154)
    - By-laws, Certificate of Incorporation, Rules and Regulations, 1948, 1953, 1971-1982, 1988 (Reel 40, Frame 310)
    - Conference on Litigative Advocacy on Behalf of Handicapped Children, June 3-4, 1985 (Reel 40, Frame 659)
    - Far West Laboratory Project, 1991 (Reel 40, Frame 951)
    - Forum on the Family Support Act, November 9-10, 1989 (Reel 41, Frame 1)
    - Foundation Center Grant Reporting Forms, March 1984-June 1987 (Reel 41, Frame 577)
    - Foundation Luncheon Group (Concerned with Programs for Children), 1973-1979 (Reel 41, Frame 730)
    - General Correspondence, 1963-1968, 1970 (Reel 42, Frame 1)
    - General Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Reel 42, Frame 233)
    - General Correspondence, 1975-1977, 1980 (Reel 42, Frame 443)
    - Grant Declinations, 1958-1965 (Reel 42, Frame 698)
    - Grant Declinations, 1971-1973 (Reel 42, Frame 800)
    - Grant Policies and Procedures, 1949-1950, 1954, 1970 (Reel 42, Frame 930)
    - Grant Summaries by Institution (A-M), 1949-1976 (Reel 42, Frame 959)
    - Grant Summaries by Institution (N-Y), 1949-1976 (Reel 43, Frame 1)
    - Grants Approved (Index), 1961-1966, 1968-1970 (Reel 43, Frame 231)
    - Grants Approved (by Date), 1946-1971 (Reel 43, Frame 241)
    - Grants Approved (by Date), 1972-1989 (Reel 43, Frame 332)
    - Grants Approved (by Institution), 1977-1989 (Reel 43, Frame 489)
    - Health and Education, 1978-1979 (Reel 43, Frame 608)
    - Historical Information, 1911, 1972, 1975, 1977, 1984, 1987 (Reel 43, Frame 635)
    - Operating Activities, 1979 (Reel 43, Frame 690)
    - Oral History Research Office, Columbia University, 1985 (Reel 43, Frame 698)
    - Overhead Allowance for Grants, 1951-1972 (Reel 43, Frame 701)
    - Planning Group Notes, 1979 (Reel 43, Frame 716)
    - Presidential Search Committee, 1995-1996 (Reel 43, Frame 739)
    - Presidential Search Recommendations, 1995-1996 (Reel 43, Frame 908)
    - Program Area, 1979 (Reel 43, Frame 1016)
    - Staff Meeting, 1979-1980 (Reel 43, Frame 1042)
    - Supporting Articles, 1978 (Reel 43, Frame 1148)
  - Child Trends, Inc., 1978-1984, 1987-1992; 2
    Child Trends, Inc. is a not-for-profit organization incorporated in New York State and devoted to "improving the quality, scope and use of statistical information concerning children; to foster collaboration among medical, behavioral and social scientists and other professionals in the advancement of multi-disciplinary and ecological approaches to the understanding of child health, learning, behavior and development, to improve the concepts and methods that guide research on the quality of children's lives and on the status and prospects of children in the United States; and to design and coordinate collaborative research projects in this field, to educate the public with respect to current trends in the circumstances of children's lives and to disseminate indicators of child health, learning, behavior and development, to support other organizations or persons with materials or services in furtherance of the above goals."
    Administrative material, surveys, and research reports ('Papers') are included in this subseries pertaining to trends in child behavior, surveys of the well-being of children, and trends in family dynamics.
    - Series 4.2 - Grant Programs - Child Trends, Inc., 1978-1984, 1987-1992 (Reel 44, Frame 1)
    - Advisory Conference, September 26-27, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 2)
    - Board of Directors Organizational Meeting, February 28, 1979 (Reel 44, Frame 71)
    - Board of Directors Organizational Meeting, October 11, 1979 (Reel 44, Frame 158)
    - Board of Directors, January 31, 1980 (Reel 44, Frame 181)
    - Board of Directors, October 9, 1980 (Reel 44, Frame 194)
    - Board of Directors, June 12, 1980 (Reel 44, Frame 238)
    - Board of Directors, February 18, 1981 (Reel 44, Frame 244)
    - Board of Directors, May 27, 1981 (Reel 44, Frame 259)
    - Board of Directors, October 28, 1981 (Reel 44, Frame 263)
    - Board of Directors, February 3, 1982 (Reel 44, Frame 265)
    - Board of Directors, June 9, 1982 (Reel 44, Frame 285)
    - Board of Directors, November 5, 1982 (Reel 44, Frame 310)
    - Board of Directors, April 7, 1983 (Reel 44, Frame 420)
    - Board of Directors, June 23, 1983 (Reel 44, Frame 525)
    - Board of Directors, October 20, 1983 (Reel 44, Frame 576)
    - Board of Directors, February 10, 1984 (Reel 44, Frame 580)
    - Budget and Expense Reports, 1978-1981 (Reel 44, Frame 582)
    - By-Laws and Incorporation, 1974, 1978, 1980-1981 (Reel 44, Frame 678)
    - Child Watch International, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 790)
    - Classification of Appropriations, 1979-1982 (Reel 44, Frame 822)
    - Development of Child Trends International, 1978-1979 (Reel 44, Frame 848)
    - Development of Childhood Social Indicators, 1982-1983 (Reel 44, Frame 919)
    - Employment Applicants, 1979 (Reel 45, Frame 1)
    - Foundation Contacts, 1978-1979 (Reel 45, Frame 10)
    - General Correspondence, 1978-1984 (Reel 45, Frame 79)
    - General Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Reel 45, Frame 301)
    - General Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Reel 45, Frame 455)
    - Interagency conference on Child and Family Statistics, April 12-13, 1984 (Reel 45, Frame 557)
    - National Health Interview Survey, 1979-1981 (Reel 45, Frame 999)
    - National Longitudinal Survey of Youth, 1987-1990 (Reel 46, Frame 1)
    - A National Study of Trends in Elementary Education, 1979 (Reel 46, Frame 289)
    - National Survey of Children, 1976-1981 (Reel 46, Frame 306)
    - Papers - 'The Condition of American Children and Youth: The Need for a Balanced Appraisal' - Presentation at the American Association for the Advancement of Science Congressional Seminar on "Our Nation's Children: The Invisible Constituency", July 27, 1982 (Reel 46, Frame 414)
    - Papers - 'Developing a Data Base and Network of Scholars for Research and Reporting on Childhood Social Indicators', 1980 (Reel 46, Frame 427)
    - Papers - 'National Information Needs in Child and Maternal Health' (Reel 46, Frame 478)
    - Papers - 'A National Longitudinal Study of Marital Disruption', 1979 (Reel 46, Frame 523)
    - Papers - 'An Organized Reporting System on Social Trends in the United States: Memorandum on Components and Procedures' (Reel 46, Frame 788)
    - Papers - 'Public Policy and the Dynamics of Foster Care: A Multi-state Study of Placement Histories', 1992 (Reel 46, Frame 843)
    - Papers - 'Trends in the Behavior and Emotional Well-Being of U.S. Children: Findings From A National Survey', 1982 (Reel 47, Frame 1)
    - Papers - 'Trends in Child Behavior Over Time' (Reel 47, Frame 47)